Ready or not
here I come
Gather here if you want to play
hide and seek
[One late, rainy night]
[At a closed theme park]
[Members have been abandoned here]
This place must be huge
Wait!
Guys!
JAEHYUN!
Where? Here?
Guys! Who are you?
Are we starting?
Is there anything in front of me?
This is terrifying
I hate this
Sigh...
Do we really have to play
hide and seek like this?
It's okay, JAEHYUN
It's okay
I'm scared
We just have to not get caught, right?
Won't it be better
if I just get caught early?
Who even plays hide and seek like this?
Please, I'm sorry
[A cruel game, with never-ending screams]
Don't scare me like that
Oh my gosh
Ready or not
here I come
Did you get caught?
Why are you in prison again?
I better go save someone
I'm coming to save you, just wait
I promise to save you!
[Phone notification]
Four members have been imprisoned
Four?
It doesn't matter if we get keys
if you're going to get caught anyway
You sure this is right?
You're going to pop out at me
I know it!
What's this?
Huh?
JAEHYUN!
[JAEHYUN's scream]
Oh my goodness
Where am I?
Finally!
[JAEHYUN's scream]
No way
Okay
Are we starting?
Huh?
[The members open their eyes, separated]
Oh no
Can we roam around?
What's this?
Sigh
[First floor]
[WOONHAK] [LEEHAN]
[Second floor]
[TAESAN] [SUNGHO] [RIWOO]
[Third floor]
[JAEHYUN]
What are we supposed to do?
Am I allowed to move now?
But what am I supposed to do?
[RIWOO carefully takes a look around]
I didn't get anything on my phone
[Second floor]
[TAESAN]
[TAESAN takes a look over the railing]
[All that greets him is pitch darkness]
[Meanwhile, JAEHYUN]
Can I move?
[Third floor]
[JAEHYUN]
[Found an elevator]
Heading down
The back doors are closing
[Heads down first]
JAEHYUN!
Can I start moving now?
[First floor]
[LEEHAN]
[LEEHAN at the first floor cafeteria]
[Elevator]
Huh? Someone is coming down
First floor, the doors are opening
[JAEHYUN]
Where did you come from?
LEEHAN, where are you?
They left me over here
I made an ugly face
the moment we started
Huh?
I made an ugly face
the moment we started
They left a spooky doll in front of me
so I screamed
Where are we supposed to hide?
Are we supposed to hide right now?
They're going to text us
[Phone notification]
Oh, I got a text
Begin looking for keys
in spots where a person can fit in
You can use the key to free yourself
or free another member if you get caught
You can only use the key once
Wait, then we're not supposed to
look for the keys
to escape this place, right?
Yeah, we just need to survive
for 4,444 seconds
[WOONHAK]
[Phone notification]
Woah
I have to head in
Begin looking for keys
in spots where a person can fit in
Spots where a person can fit...
Look for keys in spots
where a person can fit?
Spots where a person can fit?
I feel like there's
definitely something here
Is there anything here?
Let's look for the keys
I better take this with me
Got a new item
I'll hide myself with this
[First floor] [JAEHYUN, LEEHAN]
- What's upstairs?
- There is a spooky spot
Wait, in that case
we're not hiding yet, right?
Let's look for a good hiding spot
Don't we have to hide
once we find a key?
We just don't have to get caught, right?
Yeah, if you hide really well
I wonder where the others are
A photo booth?
What's this?
[Found a photo booth, where a person can fit]
Huh? We can get a key
if we take a photo
Let's take a photo!
You only get one key anyway
Don't we just need a key right now?
Yeah
[Special effects activated]
[JAEHYUN startled by the loud noise]
[Doesn't see anyone outside]
Let's take a photo, come here!
There's someone coming
[Suspicious throughout the photo shoot]
Let's just get caught
This is just...
[Right as the photo session ends]
Let's just get caught here...
[JAEHYUN's scream]
I found you
Sir...
It's my turn to seek
I'm sorry
I'm sorry!
What do we do?
They're coming for us now
We have to hide now
[Got the first key at the photo booth]
We shouldn't have done that
Let's hide back there
Near the stage?
Ready or not
Here I come
[Second floor][TAESAN]
[TAESAN looking for a hiding spot]
[Found the second key at the photo zone]
I found it
[First floor]
[JAEHYUN, LEEHAN]
Ready or not
Oh my goodness
Here I come, JAEHYUN
[Phone notification]
Hide and seek begins now,
playtime is 4,444 seconds
In the case you get caught,
you'll get sent to prison
As survival rates are important
in hide and seek
If you have a survival rate of over 50%,
ONEDOOR may receive a gift
so please do your best to survive
There's nowhere to hide
Ready or not
[Here I come, WOONHAK]
Do you want to stick together?
That's not a bad idea
[RIWOO, WOONHAK hide together]
Oh, okay
[TAESAN heads to where he started]
I have a good idea
Since there's a tree here
[Hides behind the tree and
covers himself with the black sheet]
Are you all hiding?
Yeah!
[First floor]
[JAEHYUN, LEEHAN] [RIWOO, WOONHAK]
[Second floor]
[TAESAN] [SUNGHO]
Are you all hiding?
I'm coming to get you
[First floor] [JAEHYUN, LEEHAN↓] [RIWOO, WOONHAK↑]
[Four people hiding close to each other]
[RIWOO, WOONHAK]
Hiding comes first
Yeah
Keys are important
but they're used when you get caught
[RIWOO, WOONHAK]
[JAEHYUN, LEEHAN]
I have a cold right now
so I might cough
What?
I'm going to cough
I'm so scared right now
I wonder where the others are
[SUNGHO hiding at the ticket booth on the 2nd floor]
Am I allowed to move?
[The seeker's footsteps]
[SUNGHO]
[The seeker walks away]
It's so hot
[Meanwhile, on the 1st floor]
- I think that's the seeker
- Yeah
Wait, let me take a look
Hey, they're coming closer
I can hear them from upstairs
[TAESAN hiding at the photo zone on the 2nd floor]
That must be the seeker
[TAESAN]
[Second floor]
[TAESAN, Seeker]
It's here
Maybe not?
The seeker is here, I think it's here
The seeker is coming
[TAESAN]
Shh
[Seeker's footsteps]
I think it left
[TAESAN]
[Under the black sheet
so can't see TAESAN from outside]
[The seeker's cane]
[I found you, TAESAN!]
Wow
I'm sorry
[RIWOO, WOONHAK]
[JAEHYUN, LEEHAN]
TAESAN got caught
[JAEHYUN] [SUNGHO] [RIWOO]
[TAESAN] [LEEHAN] [WOONHAK]
I can't believe I got caught first
That hurts my pride
What do these doors mean?
[If you can't escape jail within 20 minutes,
you're stuck until the game is over]
[Phone notification]
The notification sound is so loud
One of your members have been caught
I know
[Phone notification]
[JAEHYUN, LEEHAN]
I got a text
The phone light is going to show
[Seeker's footsteps]
Let's check it later
The seeker is here
It's here
I'm scared
The seeker is coming
[RIWOO, WOONHAK↑]
[JAEHYUN, LEEHAN↓]
[Seeker↓] [RIWOO, WOONHAK→]
This is crazy
They're right in front of us
[RIWOO, WOONHAK]
[JAEHYUN, LEEHAN]
[Seeker]
It's near us
[JAEHYUN, LEEHAN]
[Seeker]
[Seeker] [JAEHYUN gulping]
[RIWOO, WOONHAK]
It is right in front of us
It's right here
[Phone notification]
[LEEHAN's laugh]
We're doomed
[Phone notification]
Oh...
[The seeker heard the phone notification]
[Key hint]
Cover up the light
[Seeker]
[JAEHYUN, LEEHAN]
[RIWOO, WOONHAK]
[Seeker]
[Found JAEHYUN and LEEHAN!]
You got me
Okay
Let's go
My legs hurt
Can we put this on silent?
Who got caught?
JAEHYUN
Oh, okay
I have to change my phone
so it vibrates instead
I changed it to vibrate
[JAEHYUN] [SUNGHO] [RIWOO]
[TAESAN] [LEEHAN] [WOONHAK]
[Phone vibration]
I'm over here
[Three members have been caught]
Three members have been caught?
Whatever, I'm not going to help them
I'm not going to help them
If I leave here...
TAESAN, you already got caught?
I have a key though
[TAESAN has a key]
I'll leave in a bit
If you can't escape jail
within 20 minutes...
[Only 20 minutes to escape]
Hey, I have a key too
If I can't leave within 20 minutes,
that's game over for me
Hey, hold on
[Key hint]
This is the hint
There's a key at the merry-go-round
Do you want to go together?
- Let's go to the merry-go-round together
- Huh?
- Sure
Stay here
LEEHAN and TAESAN will leave
[TAESAN, LEEHAN escape prison]
I get scared so easy
so I'm not good with these games
[JAEHYUN] [SUNGHO] [RIWOO]
[TAESAN] [LEEHAN] [WOONHAK]
Hey
Let's check
where the seeker is first
[TAESAN, LEEHAN]
[Third floor] [Seeker]
[Seeker is currently on the third floor]
[RIWOO, WOONHAK are still on the first floor]
I feel like someone is here
[Key hint]
RIWOO!
Huh?
Stay here
I'll go save the others
Okay, you can go
I have to find a key
[WOONHAK]
[First floor]
[Footsteps come closer]
[TAESAN, LEEHAN, WOONHAK meet near the merry-go-round]
The seeker is on the third floor right now
It's coming down
Let's hide for now
Oh no
Where's the seeker?
[TAESAN, LEEHAN, WOONHAK]
[First floor]
[TAESAN, LEEHAN, WOONHAK] [Seeker]
Where's the seeker?
You guys stay here,
I'll sacrifice myself
[WOONHAK lets the others hide as he heads out]
[Seeker]
Let's keep moving forward
Since WOONHAK went that way,
let's go forward
Hold on
[Seeker's footsteps]
I don't know, what do we do?
[WOONHAK at the photo booth,
where the key was already found]
[WOONHAK]
[The seeker also heads towards the photo booth]
Three, two, one
One
It's too loud
It's way too loud
[WOONHAK]
Two
[Seeker's footsteps]
One
Hurry up
[WOONHAK taking a photo]
Three, two, one
[The seeker gets closer to WOONHAK]
[Misses WOONHAK and heads to the cafeteria]
[Done taking the photo]
Where is the key?
Give me the key
[Heads to the second floor with no reward]
[TAESAN, LEEHAN]
Where's the key?
- Should we go in there?
- You can go in
[Key hint]
[TAESAN]
[Special effect activated]
[Phone notification]
I feel like it's somewhere here
[Key hint]
Oh my goodness
This is where the key hint is
[Key hint]
Wait, hold up
Where is that?
[Found the third key in the coffin]
Did you find it?
You can head over there
Go save JAEHYUN
[Heads straight to prison after getting the key]
I found it!
I'll open the door
LEEHAN, you're the best
I can't believe you saved me
[LEEHAN saves JAEHYUN with the key]
- Should we get going?
- Let's go
[JAEHYUN] [SUNGHO] [RIWOO]
[TAESAN] [LEEHAN] [WOONHAK]
[Second floor]
[SUNGHO]
It's so hot
I'm not going to leave though
We need more than
half the members to survive
if we want to win gifts for ONEDOOR
But we currently have
more than half alive right now
so let's just keep this up
[Unknown footsteps]
Shh
[SUNGHO]
I've never been here before
[SUNGHO] [WOONHAK]
[WOONHAK's phone notification]
[Phone vibration]
[Key hint]
What's this?
[Second floor]
[WOONHAK]
I don't know
how the keys look like
[Key hint] [After checking the hint,
WOONHAK comes to the second floor locker room]
[The seeker is also on the second floor]
[SUNGHO]
[SUNGHO takes a gulp]
[WOONHAK in the locker room]
[The seeker comes closer]
[WOONHAK]
I found you!
Take me, I surrender!
Please, I'm sorry
Don't scare me like that
[WOONHAK's scream]
Oh my goodness